(Mrs Petrescu:)15 minutes can save you
15% or more on car insurance.
(Stuart:)Anybody else coming
to this thing? Uh...
- What's your name? Okay.
- Jeff.
(Penny:)Okay.
My favorite part
is your shower scene.
(Penny:)Been hearing that a lot today.
(Jeff:)I even have a screen grab
on my phone.
(Penny:)Yep, there they are.
(Leonard:)Okay, let's
keep it moving.
(Penny:)Here you go.
(Leonard:)Should've punched that guy.
(Penny:)Well, go ahead.
He's right over there.
(Leonard:)Why do you do that?
Can't you let me have my moment?
- Hello.
- Hi.
(Awkward guy:)I like your movies.
Thank you!
(Awkward guy:)I saw both of them.
(Penny:)I assume we're still
talking about the movies,
(Penny:)but after today,
who knows.
(Awkward guy:)You think I could get
a picture of us?
(Penny:)Oh, sure.
(Awkward guy:)And, uh, could you be
(Awkward guy:)giving me a kiss?